I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Tanaka-kun!
Huh?
Tanaka-kun, I heard you're
going perform at Grateful Sound?
That's so awesome! There's going
to be famous people there, right?
Chiba-senpai and Sakurai-kun's
going to be there too.
Umm, ah...
Hey, you! Stop acting like you're all that!
Yeah, just 'cause you were in some
stupid movie...You really piss us off!
Jim's movie isn't stupid!
Chiba's out sick today.
Hey!
What are you kids doing out here?!
Yikes!
Let me treat you.
Okay, strawberry milk, please.
During the second semester those guys
are gonna get beaten up by Chiba-kun.
I'd rather not let
the guys know about today.
Huh? But why?
I'd rather not cause any more
problems for the band now.
I see.
Thanks.
It's a month away from Grateful Sound...
"Live 22 'Performance Eve Festival'"
Everyone's on pins and needles.
That one...or this...
Which one's better?
Let's see...I think the simple one's better.
Yeah? Okay...
Can you tell they're really into it?
Yeah.
I think they were really
inspired by your demo tape.
You think so?
Your song has real potential.
Hey, Koyuki! It's your song, so I'm
counting on you to come up with the lyrics.
We're going to blow them away
at Grateful Sound.
Saku...
Lyrics?
What have I gotten myself into?
It's been two weeks already,
and I've got nothing.
Only ten more days until Grateful Sound...
That feeling...
If only I can remember it...
Hey!
Koyuki-kun!
Say, Momoko-sensei and I have
decided to go on a trip together,
I'm wondering if I should get circumcised.
To do it or not to do it...
I feel almost like Hamlet right now!
Ouch! Ouch, ouch! What are
you doing, Koyuki-kun?! Stop!
I see? Writing lyrics, huh?
I feel like I'm being
crushed by all this pressure.
Can you let me listen to your song?
Sure.
Here.
Aww, you should take it easy.
They say Paul McCartney heard
the lyrics for "Yesterday" in a dream.
A dream?
That night, I dreamt this dream...
"'Happy Sangokushi'
Premiere Press Conference"
...Tanaka-san?
"'Happy Sangokushi'
Premiere Press Conference"
I hope people can learn
"'Happy Sangokushi'
Premiere Press Conference"
from the rhythm of my acting.
"'Happy Sangokushi'
Premiere Press Conference"
Please teach me kindly.
Mmm...Let's see...I think it'll
be good if you keep observing me.
Yukio! Telephone!
Who is it, in the middle of the night?
Koyuki-kun, what should
I do about the circumcision?
Hmph!
To the east on the highway,
"Fishing Hole"
The man riding on a snake.
...about ten miles long...
These are some highbrow lyrics...
...Not!! This is straight
out of Jim Morrison!
Um...I'm trying my best...
Hey, don't push him so hard.
For us to compete at Grateful Sound,
each and every one of us
has to do better.
If he can't cut it,
then he should leave the band.
Koyuki-kun!
Hey, you seem kind of down today.
You seem pretty chipper today, Saito-san.
This...I gave it a shot
with my lyrics. Huh?
Sa-Saito-san!
By shucking off one skin,
my confidence has grown,
Show your courage, trust the doctors...
What the heck is this?!
Is this really the work of someone who
worships the Rocket Boys and the Beatles?
But then...
Saito-san's not at all
embarrassed by his feelings
or concerned about what others may say.
Compared to him, maybe I've been
too concerned about what others think,
and haven't been honest
in expressing myself.
You can't reach people's hearts
by being so guarded.
H-Hmm?
What's that?
"Dear Ryusuke,
The other day, when you read
my lyrics in front of everyone,
I was really embarrassed.
That's probably because those lyrics
didn't come from the heart.
This time, I wrote
what came from my heart.
It's tough to get criticized,
but I want to hear your honest opinion."
Hmm...That Koyuki...
"...but I want to hear your honest opinion.
Please listen to the MD.
This is the best I can do for now."
By shucking off one skin,
my confidence has grown...
Hmm...Huh? What's this?
Stop! You ignored the traffic light!
Hey, here's the genius!
Ryusuke was so inspired by your efforts,
he wrote these lyrics.
It's super straightforward,
just like you.
You, you think so?
But why's Saito-san singing the song?
Well, ah...
I liked the part about
shucking off one's skin.
So I went with "Slip Out."
Like how we're trying to
slip out of our current situation,
to get to something better.
-I like being wrapped with warmness
more than anything else for sure.
-You never know what fate
-I like being wrapped with warmness
more than anything else for sure.
-May bring your way...
-I'm gonna make my coming days
to be filled with laughter and joy
"1. Pany
2. Lovely Mouth
3. Beck
4. The Saw
5. Hitode"
Hitode really was something.
Yeah, their sound was really tight.
Yo! We're going out
with Hitode after the show!
We auditioned for the first Grateful Sound.
It was on a huge stage,
and we were nervous.
We've never been more nervous.
Remember this, you're going on
with no rehearsal,
so your first song is
practically thrown away.
Anyway, you guys are probably dead last
of the 94 participating bands.
You there, was it Ryusuke?
You've been scowling the whole time.
You got something against us?
-Do you want to eat yu-dofu (hot tofu)?
-Huh?
It's the most popular dish here.
That was hot, damn it!
What the hell d'ya do that for!?
Are you making fun of us?
Watch out!
Hey, you're disturbing
the other customers!
You guys, get out!
Hey, Koyuki, is your face alright?
Yeah, I'm okay. That was
just a sucker punch anyway.
I guess we won't be
playing with Hitode again.
I can understand Ryusuke-kun
feeling edgy now, but...
as much as I feel nervous about this,
I'm feeling really excited, too.
That Koyuki...He's running late!
Ryusuke, good luck!
Bring this charm with you.
Sorry! I stopped by the drugstore
and ran a bit late.
I swear...
Thank you, Granny!
"7/29 (Thursday) 11:00"
You can sleep too, you know.
Yeah, I'm okay.
It seems Saku, Koyuki, and Chiba,
couldn't sleep at all last night.
Me too.
Wow, that was a good nap.
Yeah, I got some sleep too.
What, then Taira-kun?
I couldn't sleep yesterday, either.
Is this where we're gonna?
Weren't you listening at the meeting?
This is where Belle Ame,
featuring Yoshito, will be performing.
The main stage
accommodates 20,000 people.
There's also a second stage,
with a 16,000 capacity,
and the third stage
with a 12,000 capacity.
They'll have performances
simultaneously on all three stages.
You can walk between the stages.
They're each about 10 minutes apart.
Well then, let's go!
-Yeah!
Here on the second stage, hip hop artist
Malcolm will be performing.
He's a monster of an artist who's sold
over 20 million tickets in the US.
Well, let's head on over to the
third stage, where we'll be performing.
Um, can we take a little break?
It's a cute trail.
Uh-huh.
Don't you think our stage is kind of far?
This is where we'll be performing...
The third stage.
It's the smallest of the three stages,
with a 12,000 capacity.
Hey!
Koyuki!
I wonder how many people will come out
to see an unknown band like us?
Oh, I'm so hungry! I'm dying to eat!
Here's some rice balls my mom made.
They're for everyone.
Alright! Delicious!
Here. Koyuki's mom made these rice balls.
Yeah.
Sorry...I haven't been able
to eat these past few days.
Koyuki, Saku, sorry.
I need to go talk to him.
These were Leon Syke's terms in exchange
for our appearance at Grateful Sound...
He gets all royalties for
the next 5 albums we release,
and we don't get compensated for
any tours or promotions he books us on.
Does this mean that Leon Sykes will
be endorsing us and we'll be famous?
Idiot! He's not going to spend
his money on an unknown band like ours.
It's my fault.
It's repayment for the guitar
and the dog I took.
He's going to stick us
with a crazy schedule,
then toss us out when we're through.
Probably.
But I also gave him my terms too.
What kind of terms?
If an unknown band like us gets
most attendance out of 3 stages...
What're you trying to say?
If we actually got
the most number of audience...
would you forget everything I did?
You think you can get a bigger audience
than these major artists?
Would you just shut up for a second?
Yo, you think you're in
an equal position, muthafucker?!
I wanna take my chances.
You...Are you serious?
The number of people at each stage
can be counted by the staff.
That's precious marketing material.
Put the gun down.
Huh?! Boss, don't,
don't listen to this muthafucker.
Put the gun down, okay.
Goldie, this is business.
Such a gamble...
Hey! There's no way
we can beat out Malcolm!
When I heard Koyuki's song...
I felt a possibility.
Don't go betting away
our future on your hunch!
It seems that this eve of the festival
is going to be quite
significant for all of us...
-Rock, paper, scissors!
If you can find a pastry that's not
all stale, get it for me, will ya?
Hey, if it isn't Koyuki-kun...
What are you doing out here?
I-I was going to go get some eye drops.
Are you staying at the campsite?
Uh-huh. What about you?
Koyuki-kun, can you come with me awhile?
I wonder which stage Maho will go see...
If Maho comes to see my stage,
then you give up on her
and never show your face again.
And if I agreed to that,
will you do the same?
You bet.
Good. I wanted to clear things up too.
I guess this will settle things then.
Yeah.
The Performance Eve Festival
has a jam session,
a copying contest and all kinds of fun.
Hmm. Would have been nice to participate.
Hey you guys!
What are you guys doing there?!
Oh, Aunty...
Picking my nose.
We were told that an audition band
like ours couldn't participate.
Who told you such nonsense?!
Ah, those were Ran-san's orders...
What?!
Fine. You boys come with me.
We can go in? Wow, Aunty,
you've got some clout here!
I told you!
It was my sister who originally
put together Grateful Sound.
If Maho...
Hey!
Dude, over here!
Huh, me?
Dude, I finally found you!
Yeah, the guy in the movie, alright!
He's...he's a small kid, man!
He is small!
Uh...eh...uh...
You guys are from Kneecap...
Kneecap? Right.
We're trying to play a Crush song
on the eve of the festival.
Would you play with us, if you like?
I...can't...English...
Yo!
Yoshito-kun?
Want me to translate for you?
Where the heck did Koyuki go?
I wonder if he couldn't
find any pastries...
Who's that kid?
-Hey, isn't that the boy
in the Dying Breed movie?
-Huh?! That's him?
-What was the name of their band?
-Mongo-Mongolian something?
No way! He's such a little kid!
I'm bummed!
Come on, Koyuki. I'm counting on you.
These people here are the core fans...
If you can make an impact here tonight,
they may follow us to our stage tomorrow...
Beck's fate depends on you!
Ooh! It's the Crush!
I don't know this song.
Thanks for the translation...
Get off the stage!
What did you say?? Damn you!
Please do not throw things on to the stage!
You there with the black cap,
please calm down!
It was quite a while after
the festival that Saku told me.
Later that night, Ryusuke defeated
his former bandmate Eiji.
Yo! I got the pastries.
Tomorrow's forecast?
It's supposed to be sunny. With maybe
a few showers in the afternoon.
I see...
Let's eat some pastries together!
It's not stale?
Nah.
Saku...
Yeah.
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
Ah...
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Full moon sways
Smiling in my arms for all those years
Last time, when I dove into
the audience, I fell on my head...
But I didn't get hurt!
A-ho!